(Raj:)She and I were supposed to watch
the new Avengers movie tonight,
but it was sold out.
(Raj:)So I said,
"What else do you want to do?"
(Raj:)She said,
"Let's go to a cemetery
and do it on somebody's grave."
(Howard:)Like, a random person
or somebody she knew?
(Raj:)What difference
does it make?
(Howard:)Well, if it's
(Howard:)her father's grave
and they didn't get along,
(Howard:)then you know
she holds a grudge.
(Bernadette:)The only issue is that everybody
has their own thing.
(Bernadette:)And as long
as it's two consenting adults,
(Raj:)I guess
I don't see the harm in it.
(Raj:)Well, what if it's
one consenting adult
(Raj:)and one adult who
pretends to consent
(Raj:)because he's afraid
of being alone?
(Bernadette:)Well, then I guess
bring a blanket.
(Bernadette:)The grass gets damp at night.
(Raj:)I don't know, guys.
(Raj:)Maybe this relationship
isn't for me.
(Raj:)Maybe I should break up
with her.
(chuckles) Right. You're gonna
break up with a girl
(Howard:)who has sex with you.
Can you believe this guy?
(Bernadette:)I think if Raj wants to break up
with a girl, he can do it.
(Howard:)How are you saying that
with a straight face?
(chuckling):
I don't know.